kanyidaily.com 2019-04-17

# PRIVACY POLICY | Latest Nigeria News | Kanyi Daily - Read Latest News In Nigeria Today

_Last Updated on June 2, 2018:_ At www.kanyidaily.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.kanyidaily.com and how it is used.

We understand and respect your concerns about privacy. We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time as necessary to reflect any changes in our practices.  Please check this page periodically for updates.  If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy here and notify you by means of a notice on this Website.  At all times, the most current version of our Privacy Policy shall supersede and replace all prior versions.

We will collect certain information from you when you create a user account, including your name, email address, mailing address, and month and year of birth).  We use this information to: (1) send you emails to alert you to the new developments and features of the Website (unless you opt-out of receiving such emails; (2) enhance and improve the Website; and (3) to provide advertisers and other third parties with non-personally identifiable aggregate information about our readers and their pattern of usage.

Information you choose to voluntarily publish or otherwise disclose through the Website, through comments, may be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties and we are not responsible for the use or misuse of such information.

 **Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.kanyidaily.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

We are always seeking to better understand our users and improve their experience.  When you use the Website, we may use automated technologies to collect and analyze certain types of information in order to analyze how the Website is used (so we can improve the Website).

We also collect other information related to the ways in which you interact with the Website, such as: information about the articles you view, referring and exit pages and URLs, platform type, the number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time you used the Services, and other similar information. We may also capture other data, such as search criteria and results.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons  **  
www.kanyidaily.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

We use cookies and other tracking technology, such as Flash objects (commonly called “Flash cookies”), web beacons, and pixel tags or other similar technologies to deliver or communicate with cookies and track your use of the Website.  We also may include web beacons in e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether the message has been opened. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather additional information through other methods.

You can modify your browser setting to decline cookies by visiting the Help portion of your browser’s toolbar. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in, customize, or use some features of the Website.  Flash cookies operate differently than browser cookies and cookie management tools available in a web browser will not remove flash cookies. To learn more about and manage flash cookies you can visit the Adobe website and make changes at the Global Privacy Settings Panel.

We may use de-identified information (stripped of any information that could be used to identify you) or aggregated information (e.g., demographic information and information about traffic patterns or trends among our users) for any reason and share it freely with affiliates, partners and other third parties.

We may also combine information that we collect from you with information we obtain about you from third parties and other sources.

We may share your information with other parties as follows:  
•   When we contract with third parties to perform services on our behalf;  
•   With our parent, affiliates, or subsidiaries;  
•   To protect and defend our legal rights and property, and those of our business partners, employees, agents, and contractors, including enforcement of our agreements;  
•   To protect the safety and security of our users or members of the public;  
•   For fraud or risk management purposes; or  
•   To comply with the law or legal process.  
We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including personal information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

 **  
**  
**DoubleClick DART Cookie  **

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads www.kanyidaily.com

Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.kanyidaily.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….

 **—-Google Adsense**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to automatically receive your IP address when you visit any ads that appears on www.kanyidaily.com.  Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.kanyidaily.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.kanyidaily.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Children:**  The Website is not intended for children under the age of 13.  We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children under the age of 13.

By using the Website and submitting personal information to us, you agree to permit the transfer of your personal information to countries outside your country of residence. The countries where we may transfer your personal information may have different levels of data protection than your country.

 **Links:**   The Website may contain links to third-party websites.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.  Any information you provide via those sites is subject to the privacy policies on those websites and is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

 **Contacts:**  If you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding this privacy policy, please [**contact us**](https://www.kanyidaily.com/contact-us/).
